<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stroke Victim Driving Test</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start Tests</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>

    <string name="dotinstructions">As you can see that there are groups of dots. \n Some of the
    groups have 3 dots, some 4 and some 5 dots. I want you to tap on the dots to cross out every group of 4 dots, if you make a mistake tap the same group of dots to remove the cross. I want you to complete the first row as a practice.\n As with all of these tests this is timed but it is more important to be accurate than fast.\n Start when you are ready, after you have completed the first rom tap on the "Begin test" button to start the test. </string>

    <string name="dotHelp">As you can see that there are groups of dots. \n Some of the
    groups have 3 dots, some 4 and some 5 dots. I want you to tap on the dots to cross out every group of 4 dots, if you make a mistake tap the same group of dots to remove the cross.</string>

    <string name="instructionswrong">you have missed a set of 4 dots or you have crossed
out a group of 3 or 5 dots but the task is to cross out all the groups of 4 dots </string>

    <string name="directioninstructions"> The large arrows correspond to the lorries and the small arrows to the cars. Each arrow indicates a direction of travel. I want you to position these cards so that each car is travelling in the direction indicated by the small arrow and each lorry in the direction indicated by the large arrow.\n\n Please note that the following tests will also work in this manor, tap on
        the square you think the card should be placed in the table, you can remove a card from the table by tapping and holding a square in the table and you can skip to your next card by tapping on your next carc. I will do the first one as an example.</string>

    <string name="directionhelp">The large arrows correspond to the lorries and the small arrows to the cars. Each arrow indicates a direction of travel. I want you to position these cards so that each car is travelling in the direction indicated by the small arrow and each lorry in the direction indicated by the large arrow.</string>

    <string name= "compassinstructions">This time the black arm of the compass indicates a direction of travel.  position these cards on the grid, so that
each of the vehicles on these cards. goes in the direction indicated on the compass cards. The roundabout sign is
always at the bottom. There are more cards than available spaces, so
some of the cards will not fit in. I will do the first one as an example.”</string>

    <string name="compasshelp">This time the black arm of the compass indicates a direction of travel.  position these cards on the grid, so that
each of the vehicles on these cards. goes in the direction indicated on the compass cards. The roundabout sign is
always at the bottom. There are more cards than available spaces, so
some of the cards will not fit in.</string>



    <string name= "signinstructions"> I would like you to put each road sign on the picture of the road situation which it matches best. The card in the top left shows a car stopped at a train crossing. The sign which best matches this situation is the one indicating a train crossing (which is top of your pile). So this sign (train crossing) goes with this picture. Tap the situation to put the sign on it. Then click "Start Test"</string>

    <string name= "signhelp"> I would like you to put each road sign on the picture of the road situation which it matches best. The grid shows a situation you will experience on the road, you need to match the road sign to the situation.</string>
</resources>
